(Leonard:)Oh, that's cool.
A micro-Valentine for a microbiologist. Heh.
(Leonard:)From her micro-husband.
(Leonard:)That is amazing.
How long did this take you?
Ah, about 12 hours.
I pulled an all-nighter. Heh.
(Leonard:)Oh, wow.
(Howard:)Yeah, I know, it really took a bite
out of my video-game time.
(Howard:)What are you and Penny doing?
I'm gonna take her
to a nice restaurant for dinner.
(Howard:)That's not bad, but as far as romance goes,
I think my gift hits it right out of the...
- Wanna come to dinner with us?
- Yes, please.
Okay, uh, Amy will be here shortly
expecting the perfect Valentine's gift.
(Sheldon:)So you're up, kid, dazzle me, go.
Okay, I think I have some great choices.
(Alex:)I went on Amy's Facebook page
and read her interests...